trivita.com 2016-10-12

# TriVita Wellness

$89 · free shipping free __

$119 ·  $10 off

$150 ·  $20 off

## _Last Revised 02/2015_

Scope and Consent:

You accept this Privacy Policy when you use this Web Site or any of the services or features offered on this Web Site.

Modifications to Policy:

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy, along with any related provisions, at any time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon notice. Material changes will be provided to you via e-mail or will be posted conspicuously on our Web Site (hereinafter, "Notice"). Your use of the Web Site after such Notice will be deemed acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure familiarity with its most current version. You can easily confirm whether any revisions have been posted since your last visit by checking the date on which the Policy was last revised, which is set forth at the top of this Policy. If you object to such changes, we will honor our prior privacy policies as to any data previously collected. If you disagree with the changes in our policy, however, please do not use the Web Site after the posting of such changes online.

Collection & Use of Information:

Personally Identifiable Information

You may visit our Web Site without providing and personally identifiable information. However, to use certain features or functions of the Web Site, you may be asked for certain types of personally identifiable information. As more specifically set forth below, this information allows us to administer our business and better provide products and services, as well as contact you and send you materials in certain instances.

If you place an order, you will be required to provide us with the information necessary for us to process and ship your order (e.g., your first and last name, mailing address, city, state, zip code, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, etc.).

You may also request additional information from us, which will require you to provide your contact information (e.g., name, telephone number and/or e-mail address). We will use your personal information for such purpose as well as for the purposes set forth below.

If you provide us your contact information, such as placing an order or signing up for our newsletter, we will place you in our marketing databases and you will receive informational and promotional materials from us. We will also provide your contact information to our third party independent TriVita business owners and distributors, who may also send you marketing materials. You will have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such marketing materials at any time by following the instructions in the emails.

If you do not want to disclose your personally identifiable information to us, please do not submit it. You may not be able to use all features or functions available on this Web Site if you choose not to provide us your personally identifiable information.

Information Automatically Collected

We may also automatically collect non-personally identifiable information from you when you visit the Web Site.

We collect your IP address, browser type, operating system and your navigation and click stream behavior when you visit the Web Site. We use this information to improve our Web Site and to understand how our Web Site is used. We also use this information to direct users to the TriVita website relevant to their geographic area.

We also use tracking technologies to collect and store information about your visit to our Site and your access to email communications from us. These include:

  * Server Logs — used to track the website traffic (i.e. number of website visitors, number of visitor per page, IP address, etc.). We may use this information to analyze the website traffic in order to improve our business and user experience.
  * Pixel Tags — used to track access to the email communications that we send. We may use web beacons to generate website traffic statistics to enhance our Site.

We use the information that is collected about you and your visit for analyzing trends and statistics, improving the operation of the Web Site, sending informational and promotional materials, and to help us design and enhance our products and services offerings.

Cookies:

A cookie is a small amount of data, which includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site&srquo;s computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Please note that some features on our Web Site may be impaired if you block cookies for our Site.

TriVita uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

  * Access your information when you log in to identify yourself as a previous customer or preferred member so that we can provide you with customized content in certain online areas;
  * Conduct research to improve TriVita content and services, such as length of customer visits; and 
  * Require you to re-enter your customer log in after a certain period of time has elapsed to help protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

We also use third party cookies for the Google Analytics Advertising Features as described below.

Social Web Remarketing:

We also use Facebook for remarketing purposes. We contract with Facebook to serve ads on our behalf while you are on Facebook. These ads are based on your visits to our Web Site and the cookies that we place on your computer while you are on our Web Site. You can change your cookie settings to prevent use of such cookies as set forth above.

Analytics:

Like many websites, we use Google Analytics to collect information about your use of our Web Site. This information consists of information that your web browser automatically sends to Google, such as the web address of the page that you visit and your IP address. Google may also set cookies or read preexisting cookies. This information is stored on Google's servers. Google uses this information to provide use with reports about traffic to our Web Site and your visit to our Web Site (such as the domain from which you access the internet, the web address of the website from which you linked to our site, the time and date of your visit the web pages that you view and click through). We will use this data to improve our Web Site structure and content.

Google may also use this data in accordance with their Privacy Policy, which can be found at <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>. **For more detailed information on how Google uses your data through our Site, please visit<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.**

You may opt-out of our use of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page and installing the Google Analytics browser add-on, currently made available by Google at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

Google Remarketing and Analytics Advertising Features:

We have also enabled the following Google Analytics Advertising Features: Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Remarketing with Google Analytics and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. The Google Display Network Impression Reporting uses the Google Analytics cookie to track our ad impressions and your interactions with those impressions, including the effectiveness of those ads, which generates reports for us to help us analyze our advertisements. Remarketing with Google Analytics uses the Google Analytics cookie to serve advertisements to you across the Internet based on your visit to our Web Site. Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting uses a third party cookie to collect information about our website traffic by tracking users across websites and across time, which generates a report for us to better understand our website users.

We also use the Google AdWords service to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this Web Site. Google uses cookies (or other similar identifiers) to collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web Site and your interaction with our products and services to generate targeted advertisements to you on other sites that you visit across the Internet.

If you do not want Google to collect and use this information you may visit the Google Ad Settings page (<http://www.google.com/safetycenter/tools/#manage-your-ads-preferences>) or you can also visit the website <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices> to change your consumer preferences with respect to certain online ads and to obtain further information about third party ad networks and online behavioral advertising. For the Google Analytics Advertising Features, you may also opt-out of our use of Google Analytics as described above. Please remember that changing your settings with certain browsers and ad networks will not carry your privacy choices across browsers and other ad networks.

How Your Information is Disclosed:

We may disclose the information that we collect about you when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities that may be causing injury to you, to us or to others. We may also disclose information to assist in compliance with certain laws and regulations. We also disclose your information as set forth below.

Distributors:

We may provide your contact information to our third party distributors and marketing affiliates to enable such third party distributors and marketing affiliates to contact you regarding products and services that they believe may be of interest to you.

Vendors:

We may employ vendors to perform functions on our behalf and will provide your personally identifiable information to those vendors. These vendors consist of our (i) shipping and fulfillment vendors, (ii) credit card, fraud detection, and payment processing vendors and financial institutions, (iii) call center and customer services vendors, (iv) email and marketing vendors and processors, and (iv) our website and data hosting vendors. These vendors are under contractual obligation to use confidential data only for those purposes for which they are hired.

Protection of Children:

Our Web Site is a general audience site that is not specifically designed or targeted at children. We do not knowingly collect, use or disseminate any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

Third-Party Links:

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, TriVita may provide links to various third party web sites. However, even if the third party is affiliated with TriVita, TriVita has no control over these linked sites, each of which may (or may not) have their own privacy policies and practices in place. Any information you provide to third-party web sites will be governed under the terms of each web site's privacy policy and we encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing any information to the operators of third-party web sites. TriVita has no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content, actions or policies of third-party web sites. The inclusion of third-party web sites on our Web Site in no way constitutes an endorsement of such web site's content, actions or policies. These linked sites are for your convenience and you access them at your own risk.

Nonetheless, TriVita seeks to protect the integrity of its Web Site and the links placed upon it. Therefore, TriVita requests any feedback not only on its own Web Site, but for sites it links to as well (including if a specific link does not work).

Access or Corrections to Your Information:

If you identify any inaccuracy in your personal information, or you need to make a change or would like to verify such information, please contact us so that we may update our records. Our contact information is set forth below. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to accommodate all such requests.

Security:

TriVita has implemented a number of security measures to help protect your information. Your information is stored on secured networks consistent with industry standards, and is accessible by those employees and representatives who have special access rights to such systems. Industry-standard encryption technologies are used when transferring or receiving sensitive information supplied by users. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant its complete security. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We shall not be responsible for harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality in respect to your use of our Web Site or any information you transmit to our Web Site.

Do Not Track:

We currently do not have the ability to collect cookies and other non-personally identifying information when you visit this Web Site. Due to this inability, we do not currently honor do not track requests. We do not participate in any kind of third party ad network that tracks users across websites.

Ownership of Information:

TriVita maintains full rights to information collected on this Web Site and may freely collect, use and disclose such information unless prohibited by this Privacy Policy or applicable law. In the event of a change in control of TriVita, a merger, acquisition, sale or reorganization, the information collected and maintained by TriVita may be sold and transferred to such TriVita successor as a part of such transaction without notice to you.

Questions or Comments or to Contact Us:

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or you wish to access or make changes to information about you, please call TriVita at [1-877-850-2968](tel:+18778502968) or write us at:

**TriVita, Inc.**  
_Member Services Department_  
P.O. Box 15700  
Scottsdale, AZ 85267
